They have also been released, let's start with that.
How do you feel about the anti-insurance stocks? Data has been coming in for the last two-three days.
Yesterday, SBI Live's data came today. In
fact, yesterday evening, ICS Lombard's data also
came that their premium is around 38%
and this is positive for them.
They have also issued a statement like this. So, I
want your take on insurance companies. If you can show the news about ICI Lombard, please show it
on the screen.
Vinod, I can hear it.
Good, very good morning.
Good morning to all the panelists as well. And to all your
viewers, good morning from the pure side. Definitely,
our view on the insurance sector has been
quite positive. For the
last few months, the region is quite
simple. According to this, we are looking at the growth as per which
financial awareness is increasing in the country.
Overall, I think that the
data that we saw yesterday, the growth registered by
all the companies of this segment in the month of February ranging from around 25% to 38%, will be
considered quite strong, but only which seems a
little big to me.  The concern is
visible from here right now, in which I think the
street still needs some clarity on
what impact will it have due to the surrender policy announced by IRDA. I think that
one thing is a bit uncertain. Now, overall, from a
two-three year point of view,
from a long term perspective, all the insurance
companies seem fine to me. I mean,
if we look at it earnings wise, then an earning CGR of 15 to 25 per cent
in the next two to three years.
I think that is quite possible.
Overall, I am not saying anything that can be said out
of the back. This situation is also reasonable,
so our view in this sector will also remain
positive.
Well, firstly, it is a bit technical and to find out, actually
I want to find out at a little level.